tickets available for the
entradas disponibles para la velada
4atro evening at the Santiago Bernabeu we wouldn't touch on
4atro en el Santiago bernabeo no tocaría
the tickets for the evening today
hablar hoy de las entradas de la velada
but just a quick note the
Pero simplemente un pequeño apunte los
Bernabeu boxes okay reven which
palcos del bernabeu vale reven que
would be the VIP tickets are managed by
serían las entradas VIP los gestiona el
Real Madrid who basically sell the boxes
Real Madrid que básicamente los palcos
for their own ground so
de su propio campo los venden ellos o
everything will cost the same as the day of the
sea va a salir todo igual que el día del
Metropolitano except for the
Metropolitano exceptuando las entradas
VIP tickets which as you know are always
VIP que como sabéis eso siempre corre a
covered by the clubs and if Real Madrid didn't
cargo de los clubs y si el Madrid no lo
sell them they would leave them to us don't get too
vendiese nos lo dejarían a nosotros no
excited if you were thinking of going and you were
te emociones si pensabas ir y te ha
caught napping you can't
cogido durmiendo la siesta ya no puedes
go absolutely everything was sold in
ir se han vendido absolutamente todas en
an hour sol out you filled the
una hora sol out habéis llenado el
Santiago Bernabeu A thousand thanks to everyone we
Santiago bernabeu Mil gracias a todos
want it to be an unforgettable day the
queremos que sea un día inolvidable el
rest of the tickets which are Well 880,000
resto de entradas que son Pues 880.000
in total 70 and something thousand come out on Thursday at
en total 70 y pico mil salen el jueves a
9:30 it is worth both the track tickets and the ones
las 9:30 vale tanto las de pista como la
for different sectors I confirm that
de diferentes sectores os confirmo que
the evening of the year will cost
la velada del año costará